<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Seven Wonders</string>

    <string name="taj_mahal">Taj Mahal is one of the most beautiful places in India to visit. It is listed as the UNESCO World Heritage Site. It took gigantic 22 years approximately to build and its construction was started in the year 1632 AD and lasts till 1653. It is regarded as the best example of Mughal Architecture. Construction of Taj Mahal was assigned on the shoulder of the then Architect Ustad Ahmad Lahauri by the then Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan. I would recommend you to surely visit this great piece of architecture and watch out the amazing graving on white marble. Have a look at Taj Mahal as one of the 7 wonders of the world.</string>

    <string name="petra">Petra is one of the major attractions in Jordan that was built back in about 312 BC. It is situated in the South Jordan Ma’an Governorate. It is also listed as the UNESCO World Heritage Site. This site is famous for its unique kind of rock cut architecture. The rock from where the city is carved down is of the color of the rose thus known to be the Rose City.</string>

    <string name="colosseum">Colosseum is one of the UNESCO World Heritage Sites and this was built way back in 70 to 80 AD in ancient city Rome. This land mark marked the greatest fights of the gladiators of Roman Empire. This is also named as the Flavian Amphitheatre where 50,000 to 80,000 people can sit and watch the sports and other events out there in the ancient Rome. It is considered to be as the one of the finest architecture of ancient times. This historical heritage site makes its way to be listed in the seven New Wonders of the World, the Colosseum.</string>

    <string name="machu_picchu">Machu Picchu was able to find a place in the list of the seven New Wonders of the World. If you see the place you will say it is just a valley but on examining deeply. You will find a huge and beautiful city. This was the city that was built by the Incas in 1438 AD and later on they abandoned this beautiful modern city. This site is covered in the list of UNESCO World Heritage Sites. It has become one of the major tourist attractions in the South America by the time. Must visit and watch the historical city of Incas that is also known as the “Lost City of the Incas”.</string>

    <string name="chichen_itza">Chichen Itza is the landmark of the great Maya People and is situated in Yucatan, Mexico. It was built back in 600 AD. This is a heritage site that is included in the list of the UNESCO World Heritage Sites in 1988. This site is considered to have a dense population in the old times due to its well built structure. Chichen Itza represents Mexico’s rich heritage and culture.</string>

    <string name="great_wall">The name the Great Wall of China is known to almost everyone who has studied history in school. This is the famous wall that was started building by the Chinese Emperor Qin Shihuang way back in 700 BC and later on the successors of the Chinese emperors continued its construction. It was built for the purpose of saving the China borders from foreign invasions. It is the only structure on the planet earth that is clearly visible from the space. This is the major tourist attraction in today’s time and I personally want to visit the Great Wall of China to experience Bunjee Jump over from this Great Wall. This structure is covered in the list of UNESCO World Heritage Sites.</string>

    <string name="christ_redeemer">No one can forget this beautiful and the huge statue of Jesus Christ which is known by the name “Christ the Redeemer” in which it seems Jesus is blessing us all. This statue has marked its position in the the seven New Wonders of the World. This is another big example of the modern architecture. It is one of the amazing new 7 wonders of the world 2015. It was started building in the year 1922 and completed its construction in 1931 AD. This statue of Christ the Redeemer has become the symbol of Brazilian Christianity. This statue also figures the representation of Rio de Janeiro and Brazil in the world.</string>



</resources>
